For everybody who keeps saying, it's not the guns, it's mental health.
There's always been mental health issues, ever, like since the dawn of time.
Because the brain is not perfect and because trauma is universal.
There have always been mental health issues, but there weren't always this many guns.
There weren't always this easy access to guns.
And there wasn't always this culture that you should just use guns to deal with your anger.
So we have to acknowledge that there is a chicken that came before the egg.
And then you brought in the egg and now the chicken keeps smashing the egg with the goddamn guns.
So we can't just keep saying, well, it's a mental health issue.
There will always be mental health.
There doesn't always have to be tools that people who are having mental health issues can use to misappropriate their struggles.